bookmaker.eu 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy - Bookmaker.eu

## Online Gambling Privacy Policy

BookMaker strives to ensure that it provides an accountable and secure gaming and banking experience.

BookMaker  respects the privacy of visitors to our site. Please read this Online Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our privacy practices relating to information we gather through this Web site.

Our customers can be confident that in playing on this site your personal details and financial information are kept private and are not misused.

## BookMaker Security

We are proud of our reputation for fair play and our technology ensures the secure transfer of funds. The information we collect from our visitors is stored in databases we control. Physical access to the servers on which we store visitor information is restricted. We use your credit card information only to bill you for the products and services you order from us. We don't share your credit card information with anyone, except as may be necessary to process your transactions. To protect the privacy of your credit card number and other ordering information, we encrypt this information for transit over the Internet using a Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") connection. However, as effective as modern security practices are, no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet.

Most Web browsers allow use of an SSL connection. If your browser does not support use of an SSL connection, or if you prefer not to send your credit card number over the Internet, you can place your order by calling us toll free at **1-877-827-3978**

For further information on how BookMaker uses, protects and stores information we receive from our site visitors and our customers please do not hesitate to contact our Technical team by sending an email to [contact@bookmaker.eu](mailto:contact@bookmaker.eu).

## BookMaker Privacy

BookMaker  respects your choice to play our games and works hard to ensure your total privacy. We guarantee that access to your account information is restricted to you by your unique user name and password. Your customer details are stored and managed under the strictest supervision.

  * **The information gathered by BookMaker generally falls into two categories:**
    • Information supplied by visitors to the site when they register or initiate transactions.
    • Tracking information gathered as visitors navigate through the site. Third-party providers, whose sites are featured on and accessed via our site, may gather information as well.

The information you provide us during a visit to BookMaker helps us to improve the quality and utility of our site. The more information you share with us, the better we can serve your needs.

  * **When you purchase services, we may request the following types of information:**
    • Name
    • Shipping and/or billing address
    • Credit card number or account number
    • Phone or fax number
    • Email address
    • Date of birth
    • Social Security Number
    • Driver's license number

We may need this information to process your order. If we have trouble processing your order, the contact information you provide is used to get in touch with you. We also use this contact information to provide you with updates regarding your account and/or our service. For credit card accounts, we may request a Social Security Number, the only purpose for which we'll use your Social Security Number is to confirm your identity when you inquire about or access your account.

## Protecting the Privacy of Children

BookMaker does not market to children under the age of 18. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. If you're under 18, please wait until you are 18 and come back. That time you will be welcome.

International law is very complex, and we do not know the specific laws that may apply to you where you live. We operate under strict compliance with all local laws, and urge you access our site only if you feel that you are in compliance with yours.

## Email Addresses

If you provide us your email address, from time to time we may send you emails about new products and services, or offers that we believe will interest you. Though we hope you'll find this information useful, if you do not wish to receive such email, please indicate, when you give us your email address, that you'd prefer not to receive such information or offers.

## Browser Level Information

Our Web server automatically collects your IP address when you request pages from our server. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. We also collect information on the operating system you're running on your computer and the Web browser software you're using to access our site so we can optimize our site for the most popular operating systems and Web browsers. And, because we like to know how you found our site, we keep track of where you came from.

## Information Collected by Third Parties

Our site includes links to other Web sites, and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we don't control. When you access another Web site or purchase products or services or conduct other transactions through our Web site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you're visiting or the provider of such products or services. The provider's privacy practices may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of our provider partners via a link either from the site's page or from the pages on which the products or services are offered, you should contact the provider directly for more information.

## Questions or Complaints

If you have any questions about, or complaints that concern, this Online Privacy Policy, please call Customer Service at **1-877-827-3978**. Our representatives will respond to your inquiries or help resolve any dispute concerning this Online Privacy Policy.

## Mobile Phone Numbers

If you provide us your mobile phone number, from time to time we may send you sms messages about new products and services, or offers that we believe will interest you. Though we hope you'll find this information useful, if you do not wish to receive such sms notifications, please indicate, when you give us your mobile phone number, that you'd prefer not to receive such information or offers.
